A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
The Library of Virginia
39487
37 cu. ft. and 80 boxes
League of Women Voters of Virginia
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the League of Women Voters of Virginia.
Custodial History
Accessions 24630, 27804, 37255, 41489, 43448, 44871, 45158, and 51405 are interfiled with accession 39487.
Historical Information
The League of Women Voters of Virginia was originally founded as the Equal Suffrage League of Virginia 9 November 1909. During the passage of the 19th Amendment which allowed women to vote, the League of Women Voters of the United States was formed in Chicago, Illinois, 14 February 1920. The Equal Suffrage League of Virginia served as the forerunner of the League of Women Voters of Virginia which was established 9 September 1920. The League of Women Voters of Virginia encourages women to participate in the political process and in government. The League advocates for a wide range of women's issues, as well as other political and social issues.
Scope and Content
Records, 1920-2011, of the League of Women Voters of Virginia consisting of correspondence, financial records, histories, lists, minutes, newsletters, publications, reports, studies, and other papers which document and detail the history, organization, and goals of the League of Women Voters of Virginia. Records describe the League's aim of working for women's rights and involving women in government and the political process.
Part of the collection has water damage, but is still accessible to patrons.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Board Meeting Minutes, 1952-2009.
Series II: Councils and Conventions, 1951-2011.
Series III: Adminstrative records.
Series IV: Subject files.
Series V: Local Leagues papers.
Series VI: Publications.
Contents List
- Series I: Board Meeting minutes, 1952-2009., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 1-9)
  Board Meeting minutes, 1952-2009, consists of budgets, by-laws, conference materials, correspondence, minutes, plans, reports, requests, and related papers from the board meetings of the League of Women Voters of Virginia regarding the League's operations, projects and goals. Papers include the minutes and budgets for the League of Women Voters Education Fund beginning in 1987.
  - Board meeting minutes, 1952. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1953. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1954. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1955. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-June 1956. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-November 1956 (includes program conference, 1956). (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1957. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1957. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1958. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-July 1959. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-December 1959. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1960. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1961. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-November 1961. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1962. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1962. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1963. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-December 1963. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1964. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1964. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1965. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-November 1965. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1966. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-November 1966. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1967. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1967. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-June 1968. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-November 1968. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-March 1969. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, April-November 1969. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1970. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-December 1970. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1971. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1972. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1972. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1973. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, July-November 1973. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1975. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1977. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1977. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1978. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1978. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1981. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-June 1982. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, September-December 1982. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1984. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, July-November 1984. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1985. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-December 1985. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1986. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-November 1986. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, February-March 1987. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-July 1987. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, September-November 1987. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, September 1987, related papers. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-February 1988. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, March-April 1988. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-July 1988. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, September-November 1988. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-May 1989. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, June-September 1989. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, October-November 1989. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-April 1990. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, May-August 1990. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, September-November 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-June 1991. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-November 1991. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-June 1992. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-November 1992. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-February 1993. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, March-December 1993. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1995. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1996-1997. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1998-1999. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2000. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes, January-July 2001. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes, August-December 2001. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting mailings, 2000-2001 (July-August, October, April-June), 2001-2002 (September). (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2003. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2007-2009. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting motion forms, 1991-1993. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Series II: Councils and Conventions, 1951-2011., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 10-17)
  Councils and Conventions, 1951-2011, contains budgets, correspondence, kits and workbooks, minutes, plans, reports, and related papers for the League of Women Voters of Virginia concerning the projects, plans, and operations of the League. The council met in odd-numbered years during the 1950s (a special council met in 1954), then began meeting in even-numbered years in 1962. The convention met in 1951, then in even-numbered years from 1952 to 1960, then began meeting in odd-numbered years in 1961.
  - Subseries 1: Councils, 1953-2010., 3 boxes (Box 10-12)
    - Council kit and minutes, 14 May 1953. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Special council, 4 November 1954. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Council kit and minutes, 20-21 April 1955. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Council kit and minutes, 11 April 1957. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Council kit and minutes, 14 April 1959. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Council kit and minutes, 5 April 1962. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Council kit and minutes, 5 April 1962 (with annotations). (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Council kit and minutes, 8 April 1964. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Council kit and minutes, 14 April 1966 (some pages lost). (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Council kit and minutes, 14 April 1966 (some pages lost). (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Council kit and minutes, 18-19 April 1968. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Council kit and minutes, 8-9 April 1970. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Council kit and minutes, 12-13 1972. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Council kit and minutes, 24-25 April 1974. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Council kit and minutes, 21-22 April 1976. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Council kit and minutes, 21-22 April 1976 (2 copies, 1 annotated). (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Council kit and minutes, 19-20 April 1978. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Council kit and minutes, 19-20 April 1978 (annotated copy, includes president's message). (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Council kit and minutes, 19-20 April 1978 (2 annotated copies). (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Council kit and minutes, 23-24 April 1980 (includes pre-council board meeting, agenda, and related papers). (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Council kit and minutes, 29-30 April 1982 (includes handwritten delegates list). (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Council kit and minutes, 29-30 April 1982 (includes correspondence and other papers). (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Council kit and minutes, 13-14 April 1984. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Council kit and minutes, 11-12 April 1986. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Council kit and minutes, 11-12 April 1986 (includes uncorrected minutes). (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Council kit and minutes, 6-7 May 1988. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Council kits and minutes, 6-7 May 1988 (including notes). (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Council kit and minutes, 6-7 May 1988 (including by-laws of education fund and president's packet. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Council kit and minutes, 4-5 May 1990 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Council kit and minutes, 2-3 May 1992. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Council, 2-3 May 1992, correspondence. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Council, 2-3 May 1992, related papers. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Council minutes, 7-8 May 1994 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Council kit and papers, 4-5 May 1996 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Council registrants and minutes, 2 May 1998 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Council papers, 6 May 2000 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Council minutes, 27 April 2002 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Council kit and papers, 29-30 April 2006 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Council kit and papers, 29-30 April 2006 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Council kit of Olga Hernandez, vice president, 29-30 April 2006 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Council minutes, 29-30 April 2006 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Council minutes, 3 May 2008 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Council kit, 1 May 2010 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Council workbook, 1 May 2010 (and related papers). (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2: Conventions, 1951-2011., 5 boxes (Box 13-17)
    - Convention, 11-12 May 1951. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Convention, 16-17 May 1952. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Convention, 9-10 April 1954. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Convention, 18-19 April 1956. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Convention, 26-27 March 1958. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Convention, 8-9 April 1960. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Convention, 14-15 April 1961. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Convention, 5-6 April 1963. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Convention, 8-9 April 1965. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Convention, 13-14 April 1967. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Convention, 13-14 April 1967. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Convention, 24-25 April 1969. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Convention, 20-21 April 1971. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Convention, 11-12 April 1973. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Convention, 11-12 April 1973 (annotated kits, minutes, and related papers). (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Convention, 16-17 April 1975 (annotated). (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Convention, 16-17 April 1975 (annotated). (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Convention, 22-23 April 1977. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Convention, 22-23 April 1977 (annotated kit, minutes, and related papers). (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Convention, 20-21 April 1979. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Convention, 20-21 April 1979 (annotated kit, minutes, president's address). (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Convention, 20-21 April 1979 (2 annotated copies). (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Convention, 24-25 April 1981 (2 copies, also convention report and minutes). (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Convention, 24-25 April 1981 (annotated copy). (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Convention, 15-16 April 1983 (2 copies). (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Convention, 15-16 April 1983 (minutes and related papers). (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Convention, 3-4 May 1985. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Convention, 8-9 May 1987. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Convention, 5-6 May 1989. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Convention, 5-6 May 1989 (annotated kit). (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Convention, 5-6 1989 (related papers). (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Convention, 3-4 May 1991 (2 copies). (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Convention, 3-4 May 1991 (annotated copy and related papers). (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Convention, 15-16 May 1993 (3 copies, 1 annotated and 1 with a corrected report). (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Convention, 15-16 May 1993 (related papers, including minutes). (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Convention, 15-16 May 1993 (accomodations). (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Convention, 6-7 May 1995. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Convention, 3-4 May 1997. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Convention, 1-2 May 1999. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Convention, 5-6 May 2001. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Convention (papers), 5-6 May 2001. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Convention (prep notes), 2-4 May 2003. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Convention kit (Olga Hernandez), 2-4 May 2003. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Convention (papers, including directions to the board and surveys), 2-4 May 2003. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Convention (prep notes and papers), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Convention kit, 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Convention kit (annotated), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Convention kit (Frances Schutz, LWV Va office manager), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Convention kit (Olga Hernandez, LWV Va organization), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Convention (president's packet?), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Convention (papers), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Convention (minutes), 30 April-1 May 2005. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Convention kit (Lulu Meese, president), 28-29 April 2007. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Convention kit, 2-3 May 2009. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Convention (Olga Hernandez), 30 April-1 May 2011. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Council/Convention papers., 1 box (Box 17)
    - Convention and council planning. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Convention [and council] manual, 1986. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Convention/council manual, ca. 1998. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Convention/council manual, 2000. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Convention/council manual, 2001. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Council/Convention parliamentarians. (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Series III: Administrative records., Extent: 21 boxes. (Box 18-38)
  Administrative records includes by-laws, budget and financial papers, clippings, correspondence, insurance papers, leases, lists, publications, questionnaires, reports, rosters, studies, surveys, and related papers concerning the organization and operation of the League of Women Voters of Virginia, including committees, conferences, development, education fund, financial matters, lobbying, membership, officers, policies and procedures, programs, public relations, roundtables, workshops, and other topics regarding women's role in politics and government and women's rights. Records also include materials from the League of Women Voters of the United States.
  - Subseries 1: By-laws., 1 box (Box 18)
    - By-laws and revisions, 1951-1963, 1966-1967. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - By-laws and revisions, 1967-1977. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - By-laws and revisions, 1982-1993. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - By-laws and revisions, 2004-2005, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Presidents., 2 boxes (Box 18-19)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1954-1957. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1958. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1959. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1960. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1961-1964. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1967-1969. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1970-1971. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1977, 1980-1990, 1993-1997. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and papers, 2000, 2004-2009. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and papers, no date. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - President's packet, 2004-2006. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - President's workbook, part I. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - President's workbook, part II. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - President's workbook, part III. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Successor files, part I. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Successor files, part II. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Finance., 3 boxes (Box 19-21)
    - Budget papers, 1956-1961. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Budget papers, 1962. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Budget papers, 1963. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Budget papers, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Budget papers, 1965-1966. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Budget papers, 1967-1969. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Budget papers, 1970-1974. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Budget papers, 1975-1978. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Budget papers, 1979. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Budget papers, 1980. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Budget papers, 1981. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Budget papers, 1982. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Budget papers, 1983-1984. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Budget papers, 1985. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Budget papers, 1986. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Budget papers, 1987-1988. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Budget papers, 1989. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Budget papers, 198[-]. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Budget papers, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Budget papers, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Budget papers, 1992-1995. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Budget papers, 1996. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Budget papers, 1997, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Budget papers, 199[-]. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Budget papers, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Budget papers, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Budget papers, 2006-2007. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1952-1955, 1958, 1963. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - SCC notices of assessment, 1979-1988. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Disclosure reports, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Tax Commission report, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Contributors, 1983-1993. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fundraising, 1979-1993. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising, 1994-1996, 2000-2001, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Solicitations, 1983-1987, 1991-1993. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Direct mail fund, 1984-1987, 1991, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Solicitations of Contributions Act, 1977-1979. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Revenue services, 1975-1977. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Calendar planning, 1996. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 4: Business., 1 box (Box 21)
    - State tax and postal rates, 1977, 1979. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Insurance, 1986-1987, 1991-1994. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Lease, Bon Air Green, 1991, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Lease, Falls Church, 1993-1995. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 5: Policies and procedures., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Policies and procedures, 1964, 1966. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Policies and procedures, 1981-1997, no date. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 6: Organization., 2 boxes (Box 21-22)
    - Chairman, 1955-1957. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Committee, 1960-1962. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Papers, 1963-1966. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1969-1972, 1976, 1979-1984. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Papers, 1985. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1986-1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1995-1997, no date. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 7: Development., 1 box (Box 22)
    - Development, 1979-1989. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Development, 1990-1994. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Development, 1995. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Development, 1996. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 8: Membership., 1 box (Box 22)
    - Papers, 1964-1965. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Papers, 1966-1968. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Papers, 1974-1979. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Papers, 1982, 1985-1988. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Papers, 1990-1991. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Papers, 1992-1996. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Papers, 2004-2005, 2010, no date. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 9: Voters Service., 1 box (Box 23)
    - Chairman, 1956-1957. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Voters service, 1959-1963. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Voters service, January-August 1964. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Voters service, September-no month 1964. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Voters service, 1965-1966. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Voters service, 1967-1969. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Voters service, 1970-1978. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Voters service, 1979-1984. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Voters service, 1985-1988. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Voters service, 1991-1995. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Voters service, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Candidate questionnaires, 1964. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Candidate questionnaires, 1965. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Candidate questionnaires, 1965. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 10: Nominating Committee., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Papers, 1957-1958. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1978-1982. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Papers, 1983-1985. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1986. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1987-1988. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Papers, 1989-1992. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Papers, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1995-1996. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Papers, 2000, 2006-2007, no date. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 11: Legislative Committee., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Papers, 1948, 1955-1957. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Papers, 1958. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Papers, 1963-1964. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Legislative coordinator, 1981-1990. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 12: Public Relations., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Papers, 1956-1964. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Papers, 1974-1979, 1983-1986. (Box 24, Folder 15)